A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series III: Financial Records, 1902-1981
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Freight Statements, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1958-1959 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1960-1962 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - "Freight Statements" Binder, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Loom Order, September 1922 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Deposits to the First National Bank, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Payment Receipts, Washington Mills, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Payment Receipts, Washington Mills, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Deposits to the First National Bank, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Deposits to the First National Bank, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Purchase Requisitions, March 1973 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Purchase Requisitions, April 1973 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Purchase Requisitions, May 1973 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Purchase Requisitions, June 1973 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Purchase Requisitions, July 1973 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Purchase Requisitions, August 1973 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Purchase Requisitions, September 1973 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Purchase Requisitions, October 1973 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Purchase Requisitions, November 1973 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Purchase Requisitions, December 1973 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Purchase Requisitions, January 1974 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Purchase Requisitions, February 1974 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Order Form Booklets, 1902-1921 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Weekly Learner Pay Report, July 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 1st Period P/E, 11-3-80 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 2nd Period P/E, November 29, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 3rd Period P/E, December 27, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 4th Period P/E, January 31, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 5th Period P/E, February 28, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 6th Period P/E, March 31, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 7th Period P/E, May 2, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 8th Period P/E, May 30, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Ext. and Internal Invoices -- 9th Period P/E, July 4, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Intercompany Invoices -- 10th Period P/E, August 8, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Intercompany and External Invoices -- 11th Period P/E, September 5, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Invoices Yarn and Cloth -- 12th Period P/E, October 3, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Spending, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Statements, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Supply Expense Issue (Daily) (folder 1 of 3), October- December 1979 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Supply Expense Issue (Daily) (folder 2 of 3), January- April 1980 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Supply Expense Issue (Daily) (folder 3 of 3), May- September 1980 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Income, November 1979- October 1980 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Purchase Requisitions (folder 1 of 3), 1970 (Box 135, Folder 71)
  - Purchase Requisitions (folder 2 of 3), 1970 (Box 135, Folder 72)
  - Purchase Requisitions (folder 3 of 3), 1970 (Box 135, Folder 73)
  - Shipping Records, May-June 1918 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Order Book, 1903-1904 (Box 129)
  - Order Records, 1904? (Box 74)
  - Order Book, 1904-1905 (Box 132)
  - Order Book, 1905 (Box 75)
  - Order Book, 1905? (Box 75)
  - Order Records, 1906 (Box 75)
  - Orders, 1906 (Box 75)
  - Order Records, 1906-1907 (Box 76)
  - Order Book, 1906-1907 (Box 76)
  - Order Records, 1906-09 (Box 76)
  - Order Book, 1908 (Box 130)
  - Order Records, 1908 (Box 130)
  - Order Records, 1908-1909 (Box 76)
  - Order Records, 1908-1909 (Box 134)
  - Order Book, 1909 (Box 77)
  - Order Records, 1909 (Box 58)
  - Order Records, 1909 (Box 77)
  - Order Book, 1909-1910 (Box 130)
  - Order Records, 1909-1910 (Box 77)
  - Order Records, 1909-1910 (Box 77)
  - Order Records, 1909- 1922 (Box 77)
  - Money earned through entertainment, 1910 (Box 129)
  - Order Records, 1910 (Box 77)
  - Order Book, 1910 (Box 78)
  - Order Records, 1910-1911 (Box 78)
  - Order Records, 1911 (Box 100)
  - Order/ Payment Records and Extension Index, 1911-1912 (Box 132)
  - Order Book, 1912 (Box 100)
  - Orders, 1912 (Box 132)
  - Order Records, 1912 (Box 79)
  - Order Records, 1912 (Box 130)
  - Orders, 1912-1913 (Box 103)
  - Order Records, 1912-1913 (Box 105)
  - Order Records, 1912-1914 (Box 56)
  - Order Records, 1913 (Box 131)
  - Orders, 1913 (Box 131)
  - Orders, 1913-1914 (Box 105)
  - Order Records, 1913-1914 (Box 105)
  - Order Book, 1914 (Box 56)
  - Orders Records, 1914 (Box 134)
  - Order Records, 1914-1915 (Box 129)
  - Order Book, 1914-1915 (Box 134)
  - Order Records, 1914-1915 (Box 134)
  - Order Records, 1915 (Box 56)
  - Orders, 1915 (Box 134)
  - Order Records, 1915 (Box 105)
  - Order Book, 1915-1916 (Box 134)
  - Order Records, 1916 (Box 107)
  - Order Records, 1916-1917 (Box 107)
  - Order Records, 1916-1917 (Box 55)
  - Order/ Shipping Records, 1917-1919 (Box 79)
  - Air Reduction Sales Co., 1917-1926 (Box 129)
  - Order Records, 1918 (Box 107)
  - Order Records, 1927-1935 (Box 79)
  - Index #'s for orders from divers companys, 1935-1946 (Box 110)
  - Order Records, 1943-1944 (Box 106)
  - Order Book, 1944 (Box 130)
  - Company Orders, 1950-1952 (Box 110)
  - Order Records (Box 80)
  - Index Order Books 3-4 (Box 56)
  - Order/ Delivery Records, 1905-1906 (Box 103)
  - Order/ Shipping Records, 1947-1949 (Box 80)
  - Extension Index, No Date, Ledger 1A (Box 56)
  - Order Index (Box 56)
  - Index -- Business Transactions (?) (Box 56)
  - Extension Index (Box 110)
  - Extension Index (Box 56)
  - Extension Index, No Date, Not Lesters (Box 110)
  - Extension Index, No Date, Not Lesters (Box 56)
  - Invoices/ Order Book #2 (Box 107)
  - Invoices?, 1903 (Box 131)
  - Invoices, 1905-1906 (Box 119)
  - Invoices?, 1906 (Box 131)
  - Invoices, 1909-1910 (Box 130)
  - Invoices, 1911 (Box 58)
  - Invoices, 1911-1912 (Box 56)
  - Invoices, 1912-1913 (Box 59)
  - Invoices, 1917-1919 (Box 58)
  - Memo Invoices, 1968-1969 (Box 113)
  - Freight Invoices, 1974 (Box 108)
  - Freight Invoices, 1974-1975 (Box 108)
  - Town of Fries Financial Records, 1902-1908 (Box 60)
  - Company Store Records?, 1906-1908 (Box 118)
  - YMCA Membership, 1923-1928 (Box 61)
  - YMCA Monthly Membership Dues, 1928-1932 (Box 61)
  - YMCA Monthly Membership Dues, 1932-1937 (Box 61)
  - YMCA and Fries Theater Records (folder 1 of 4), 1935- 1936 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - YMCA and Fries Theater Records (folder 2 of 4), 1937 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - YMCA and Fries Theater Records (folder 3 of 4), 1938-1939 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - YMCA and Fries Theater Records (folder 4 of 4), 1940-1948 (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - YMCA Monthly Reports (folder 1 of 2), 1942-1943 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - YMCA Monthly Reports (folder 2 of 2), 1944-1947 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Employee Records (Rent in Company-owned housing), 1958-1974 (Box 57)
  - Weekly and Monthly House Payments, 1965-1969 (Box 61)
  - Methodist Church (repair fund?), 191?-1934 (Box 61)
  - Shipping Records, 1904-1907 (Box 134)
  - Shipping Records, 1905 (Box 131)
  - Shipping Records, ~1909-1910 (Box 57)
  - Shipping, 1912-1913 (Box 115)
  - Shipping Records, 1919-1925 (Box 131)
  - Shipping Records, 1922-1923 (Box 115)
  - Shipping Records, 1931-1935 (Box 133)
  - Shipping/ Delivery Records, 1935-1937 (Box 106)
  - J. C. Penny's material concerning shipping, 1939-1988 (Box 55)
  - Shipping Records, 1941-? (Box 57)
  - Shipping Records, 1944 (Box 118)
  - Shipping Records, 1944-1945 (Box 106)
  - Shipping Records, 1948 (Box 115)
  - Shipping Records, 1951-1952 (Box 63)
  - Shipping Records, January 1952- June 1952 (Box 112)
  - Shipments, August 1975 (Box 113)
  - Shipments, September 1975 (Box 62)
  - Shipments, February 1976 (Box 62)
  - Shipments, March 1976 (Box 113)
  - Shipments, April 1976 (Box 62)
  - Shipments, November 1976 (Box 62)
  - Shipments, December 1976 (Box 62)
  - C.H. Boye Shipper Washington Mills (Box 55)
  - Delivery Records, 1903 (Box 110)
  - Deliveries, 1903-1905 (Box 104)
  - Delivery Receipts, 1916 (Box 115)
  - Delivery Receipts, 1916 (Box 60)
  - Delivery Records from Washington Mills Co., Mayodan, NC, 1923-1927 (Box 99)
  - Delivery Records, 1948-1949 (Box 133)
  - Delivery Records/ Inventory?, 1948-1950 (Box 131)
  - Delivery Records, 1952-1953 (Box 114)
  - Delivery Receipts (Box 60)
  - Compressed/ Non-Compressed, 1921-1924 (Box 133)
  - Compressed and Non-Compressed Ties Shipping/ Delivery Records, 1922-1933 (Box 116)
  - Compressed Non-Compressed Record, 1936 (Box 64)
  - Company Balance Book, 1904-1907 (Box 84)
  - Company Cash Balances as Rep by Ind. Balance Book, 1906-1927 (Box 84)
  - Comprehensive Record of Company Expenses, 1907-1921 (Box 84)
  - Shop, Warehouse, Outside, Office, Supply Room Ledger, 1935-1973 (Box 132)
  - Office Expenses, 1949-1960? (Box 133)
  - Balance Expenditures Personnel/ Company Tab, 1915-1918 (Box 84)
  - (Balance) Expenditures Personnel Company Tab, 1922-1925 (Box 82)
  - (Balance) Expenditures, 1925-1927 (Box 82)
  - Company (Balance) Expenditures, 1927-1930 (Box 82)
  - Balance Expenditures Personnel/ Company Tab, 1930-1933 (Box 87)
  - Balance Book, January 1933- September 1935 (Box 133)
  - Balance Expenditures, 1933-1936 (Box 87)
  - Balance Expenditures, 1936-1939 (Box 87)
  - Company Balance Book, 1944-1946 (Box 88)
  - Balance Expenditures, 1974-1975 (Box 88)
  - Company Tab, 1904-1905 (Box 85)
  - Company Tab Personnel, 1907-1909 (Box 85)
  - Company Tab, 1911-1914 (Box 85)
  - Cash Book Summary, 1918 (Box 85)
  - Cash #5 Company Tab, 1918-1921 (Box 86)
  - (Employees Company) Company Tab, 1939-1941 (Box 86)
  - Cash Book No. 12 Company Tab, 1941-1944 (Box 88)
  - Cash Book #14 Company Tab, 1944-1947 (Box 92)
  - Company Tab, 1947-1950 (Box 92)
  - Company Tab, 1949-1952 (Box 93)
  - Co. Cash Book, 1952-1954 (Box 119)
  - Company Tab, 1952-1955 (Box 93)
  - Company Tab, 1955-1958 (Box 102)
  - Company Tab, 1958-1960 (Box 102)
  - Company Tab, 1960-1962 (Box 91)
  - Company Tab, 1962-1964 (Box 91)
  - Company Tab, 1964-1966 (Box 90)
  - Company Tab, 1966-1968 (Box 90)
  - Employee's Company Tabs, 1968-1970 (Box 104)
  - Payroll Avalon Mills, 1903-1904 (Box 97)
  - Suspended Accounts not in Balance Expenditures, 1903-1904 (Box 97)
  - Suspended Accounts, 1904 (Box 98)
  - Payroll, 1904 (Box 99)
  - Suspended Accounts, 1905 (Box 103)
  - Payroll, 1905 (Box 101)
  - Payroll? Personnel (By Employee), 1905 (Box 101)
  - Payroll/ Accounts Receiving Memos, 1914-1915 (Box 56)
  - Unclaimed Wages Ledger, 1916-1956 (Box 118)
  - Payroll, 1932-1933 (Box 119)
  - Payroll, 1932-1933 (Box 119)
  - Payroll, 1935-1936 (Box 64)
  - Payroll?, 1939-1940 (Box 133)
  - Bond and Savings Records, 1942-1954 (Box 119)
  - Outstanding Payroll Checks, 1943-1945 (Box 133)
  - Payroll Personnel Timesheets, April- May 1950 (Box 116)
  - Weekly Payroll, 1972 (Box 107)
  - Paymaster Checks, 1973 (Box 109)
  - Paymaster Checks, 1974-1975 (Box 109)
  - Payroll, 1976 (Box 106)
  - Cloth Room Accounts, 1903-1904 (Box 89)
  - (Cotton Purchases) Monthly Cotton Book, 1903-1940 (Box 55)
  - Cloth Room Accounts, 1904-1912 (Box 89)
  - Payment Records, 1906-1907 (Box 89)
  - Bills of Lading, 1907 (Box 134)
  - Bills of Lading, 1916 (Box 57)
  - Brooks Transportation, 1947-1948 (Box 58)
  - Oil Book, 1916-1924 (Box 60)
  - Voucher Records, 1920-1921 (Box 115)
  - Cost Sheet Records, 1923-1934 (Box 104)
  - Strips Loaded in Cars, 1925-1927 (Box 56)
  - Cotton Freight Ledger, 1932 (Box 112)
  - Lumber Book, 1929-1931 (Box 130)
  - Lumber Book, 1934-1937 (Box 60)
  - Lumber Order Book, 1937-1941 (Box 64)
  - Cotton Bought Records, 1940-1965 (Box 55)
  - Freight Records, 1945 (Box 58)
  - Check Receipts, 1903-1910 (Box 133)
  - Draft Notices, October 13, 1944- June 18, 1958 (Box 129)
  - Bank Draft Notices, 1951-1952 (Box 59)
  - Bank Draft Notices, 1954-1955 (Box 59)
  - Draft Notices, May 1, 1959-April 28, 1960 (Box 129)
  - Freight Bills, 1966-67 (Box 109)
  - Cotton Purchased, 1967-76 (Box 57)
  - Freight Received, 1970-1972 (Box 61)
  - Accounts Payable Knitting, 1971 (Box 111)
  - Freight Received, 1972-1973 (Box 61)
  - Cotton Enroute Notices, 1976 (Box 113)
  - Coal Book (Box 60)
  - Extension Index Bills of Lading (Box 114)
  - Accounting Records, 1950-1952 (Box 115)
  - Account Book, 1910-1911 (Box 59)
  - Receipts, 1917-1918 (Box 64)
  - Credit Memos, 1934-1976 (Box 108)
  - SE Ledger (Box 83)
  - Orders Consigned to Leslie, Evans and Co., 1921-1928 (Box 83)
  - Records of Stock, Production, Deliveries, and Shipments, 1904-1909 (Box 83)
  - Extension Index (Box 83)
  - Order Records, 1912-1913 (Box 137)
  - Shipping Records, 1907 (Box 137)
  - Order Records, 1907-1908 (Box 137)
  - Shipping Records, 1908-1913 (Box 138)
  - Orders, 1910 (Box 138)
  - Cotton Sheets, November 1948- July 1949 (Box 138)
  - Shipping, 1903-1906 (Box 139)
  - Cardroom Bank Book, 1941 (Box 139)
  - Payroll, 1940-1942 (Box 139)
  - Payroll, 1939-1942 (Box 139)
  - Order Book, 1943 (Box 139)
  - Account Sheets (Box 140)
  - Account Sheets (Box 140)
  - Account Sheets (Box 141)
  - Account Sheets (Box 141)
  - Account Sheets (Box 142)
  - Payroll Records, Accounts "E", ~1910-1940 (Box 142)
  - Account Sheets "D" (Box 143)
  - Employee Account Sheets, 1919-1930's (Box 143)
  - Payroll Records, 1930's (Box 144)
  - Payroll, 1949-1957 (Box 145)
  - Account Sheets, 1949-1953 (Box 145)
  - Account Sheets (Box 146)
  - Account Sheets (Box 146)
  - Payroll, May 1976 (Box 147)
  - Payroll, May 1976 (Box 147)
  - Account Records A-F (Box 101)
  - Freight Records, 1952-1953 (Box 101)
  - Account Records Ak-An (Box 150)
  - Account Records Ak-Ay (Box 150)
  - Account Records An-At (Box 150)
  - Account Records, 1935-1948 (Box 150)
  - Account Sheets, 1921-1925 (Box 150)
  - Account Sheets "A", 1919-1941 (Box 151)
  - Employees' Earnings Reports, 1969 (Box 152)
  - Employees' Earning Records, 1969 (Box 152)
  - Employees' Earnings Reports, 1969 (Box 154)
  - Employees' Earnings Reports, 1969 (Box 154)
  - Employees' Earnings Records, 1969 (Box 154)
  - Employees' Earning Records, 1969 (Box 154)
  - Fries (E. Wood) Weekly Payroll Upload -- Deduction Lists -- Payroll Register, January 1970 (Box 153)
  - Fries (E. Wood) Weekly Payroll Upload -- Deduction Lists -- Payroll Register, January 1970 (Box 153)
  - Payroll (Vacation Pay), June 1976 (Box 153)
  - Payroll (Vacation Pay), June 1976 (Box 153)
  - "Paymaster" Binders (#1), October- December 1918 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - "Paymaster" Binders (#1), 1919 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "Paymaster" Binders (#1), 1920 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - "Paymaster" Binders (#1), 1921 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, October 1921- March 1922 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, April- December 1922 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January-March 1923 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, April- July 1923 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, August-September 1923 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, October- December 1923 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January-March 1924 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, April- June 1924 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, July- October 1924 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January 1926 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, February-April 1926 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, May-July 1926 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, August- October 1926 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, November- December 1926 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January-March 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, April-June 1927 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Paymaster" Binders, July-August 1927 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, September- October 1927 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, November- December 1927 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January- February 1928 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, March-April 1928 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, May-June 1928 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, July- August 1928 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, September- October 1928 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, November- December 1928 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January-March 1929 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, April-June 1929 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, July- August 1929 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, September- October 1929 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, November- December 1929 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January 1930 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, March 23- December 1963 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January- May 1964 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, June- December 1964 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, January-April 1966 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, May- December 1966 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - "Paymaster" Binder, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1921-1925 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1926-1928 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1929-1931 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1932-1934 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1935-1939 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - "Payroll Reports and Statistics (Miscellaneous) Binder (1), 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, November 1957- March 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, April- August 1958 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, September 1958- January 1959 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, February-July 1959 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, August- December 1959 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, January-February 1962 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, March- July 1962 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - "Payroll Distribution" Binder, August- December 1962 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Payroll Report, 1978- 1979 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Payroll Report, 1979- 1980 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Personnel Records, 1902-1975
  - "Social Security" Binders, 1936-37 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - "Social Security" Binders [Miscellaneous reports], 1938-39 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - "Social Security" Binders [Miscellaneous reports], 1940-49 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - "Social Security" Binders [Miscellaneous reports], 1950-56 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - "Garnishees" (Summons) Binders, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Weekly time records, June 1, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Weekly time records (folder 1 of 2), June 8, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Weekly time records (folder 2 of 2), June 8, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Weekly time records (folder 1 of 2), June 8, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Weekly time records (folder 2 of 2), June 8, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Weekly time records, June 8, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    This material is restricted due to personally identifiable information. Contact Special Collections for additional information.
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - "Hospital Insurance" Binders, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - "Life Insurance" Binders [Security Life and Trust Co., Winston-Salem, N.C.], 1961-74 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Weekly time records (folder 1 of 2), March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Weekly time records (folder 2 of 2), March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Weekly time records, March 2, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Weekly time records, March 30, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Weekly time records, March 30, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Weekly time records, March 30, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Weekly time records, March 30, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, March 27-July 31 1942 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, August 7- December 31, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 8- March 26, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, April 2 - July 30, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, August 6- November 5, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, November 6- December 23, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 7- December 29, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 12 - December 28, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 11- December 27, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 10- December 23, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 16- December 23, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 7- December 30, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 13- December 27, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 6- December 26, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - "Defense Bonds" Binder, January 2- December 23, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 25)